<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dennis' Projects</title><link>/dennis-site/</link><description>Recent content on Dennis' Projects</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/dennis-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/dennis-site/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/about/</guid><description>ABOUT Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m a uni student with a lot of free time on my hands and a lot of stuff I wanna do This website&amp;rsquo;s here primarily as a way for my friends and colleagues to surf through the projects I work on a lot easier Primarily, I&amp;rsquo;ll be posting art and writing but I worked on a lot of different stuff so we&amp;rsquo;ll see what ends up going up</description></item><item><title>All Alone At The End</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/attheend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/attheend/</guid><description>You’re looking at the end now, And it’s still so far away. But it always looks so lonely there, Why is nobody there, But you?
You’re looking behind you now, At things you can never change. If only you could’ve been not you, But if “not you”, then who?
You’re looking at yourself now, The one who’s never good enough, The one with the excuses. What use is, He?
You’re looking at your friends now No flaws or struggles of their own.</description></item><item><title>An Endless Jigsaw</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/endlessjigsaw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/endlessjigsaw/</guid><description>He lays himself out on the kitchen floor, Looking over old history, He looks different each time, How different is he really?
There’s pieces missing he realises, And yet no gaps left to fill, What could he be missing, What did he choose to kill?
He seems so much bigger now, Across the floor, his pieces sprawl, Where did the new ones come from, Was he really ever that small?</description></item><item><title>If There Were No Stars</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/nostars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/nostars/</guid><description>The phone grew heavy in his hand, threatening to drop from his grip, from the cliff, into that endless expanse below. He couldn’t even see the floor from here; no matter where he looked, it was all the same murky black abyss. At least if he looked up there were stars, dots of light, of something piercing through all of that nothing. Down there… It was just empty.
“Adam?” Adessa’s voice called tentatively from behind him.</description></item><item><title>Mother</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/mother/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/mother/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;In 20 days, my mum dies in an accident on her way home from work. She finishes work at 4 so chances are I&amp;rsquo;ll be in a lecture or doing homework when it happens. My dad would rush home from work when he&amp;rsquo;s called but he works nearly an hour away, by the time he arrives mum might already be dead or at least very close to death. The hospital would do anything they could to help her but eventually she&amp;rsquo;ll succumb to her injuries and my dad will watch her die and he&amp;rsquo;d cry.</description></item><item><title>Project 1: Setting up the website</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/setup-helloworld/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/setup-helloworld/</guid><description>Get the website made and hosted locally: Done Get the website up on Git: Done Create a list of backdated projects to post: Done Learn how to post images and videos: Not done Work out how to tag posts: Not done Create a branching structure for posts: Not done
Backdated project list (to add): Art Everything in the folder</description></item><item><title>Skulduggery Pleasant and Failed Promises</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/skulduggery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/skulduggery/</guid><description>Valkyrie &amp;amp; Skulduggery I’d like to start this review with a brief discussion of the main two characters as it pretty well encompasses everything I like about this series.
Valkyrie is likely the most consistent main character throughout the series (as long as you separate her from her two alter egos, Stephanie and Darquesse), she’s:
● Self absorbed
● Hypocritical
● Obsessed with Skulduggery
● And she never thinks too far ahead</description></item><item><title>Solitude, Death's Neighbour</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/solitude/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/solitude/</guid><description>A bar this time, old-fashioned but still younger than the man sat at it. He must’ve been getting into his 60’s now, patches of grey hair hung desperately from his loosening skin. There was a drink in his hand, but Adam didn’t know enough about alcohol to identify it. The man called him over, the wave of his hand causing his overcoat to ruffle slightly, the only noise in what should’ve been an active bar.</description></item><item><title>The Fall of the Northern Hills</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/tfotnh/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/tfotnh/</guid><description>Lowri 1 Lowri had grown up on stories of princes and princesses, but she was not one of them, nor had she ever been deluded enough to believe she was. She lived a life of endless work, and she earned what she got, and she was proud of that fact. She’d become an Adventurer in hopes of bettering her station and, after a decade of training and fighting and nearly dying, her wishes had been granted.</description></item><item><title>Wetherspoons</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/wetherspoons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/wetherspoons/</guid><description>Here, in Wetherspoons,
Misbegotten, I pour beer,
Can I leave yet? No.</description></item><item><title>Zombies are so fucking cool man, you just don't get it</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/zombiesessay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/zombiesessay/</guid><description>Minor spoilers ahead for: The Walking Dead, The Stuff, I Am Legend, One Punch Man
Major spoilers ahead for: The Night of the Living Dead
(Yeah, we’re not talking about Frankenstein, he’s not a real Zombie, fight me)
Structure · Zombies in myth
· The Night of the Living Dead
· Modern Zombie media
· My issues with modern Zombies
· The Bite
· Plato’s Ideal Zombie Story
· Summary</description></item></channel></rss>