<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>One-Shot on Dennis' Projects</title><link>/dennis-site/tags/one-shot/</link><description>Recent content in One-Shot on Dennis' Projects</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/dennis-site/tags/one-shot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Fall of the Northern Hills</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/tfotnh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/tfotnh/</guid><description>Lowri 1 Lowri had grown up on stories of princes and princesses, but she was not one of them, nor had she ever been deluded enough to believe she was. She lived a life of endless work, and she earned what she got, and she was proud of that fact. She’d become an Adventurer in hopes of bettering her station and, after a decade of training and fighting and nearly dying, her wishes had been granted.</description></item><item><title>Solitude, Death's Neighbour</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/solitude/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/solitude/</guid><description>A bar this time, old-fashioned but still younger than the man sat at it. He must’ve been getting into his 60’s now, patches of grey hair hung desperately from his loosening skin. There was a drink in his hand, but Adam didn’t know enough about alcohol to identify it. The man called him over, the wave of his hand causing his overcoat to ruffle slightly, the only noise in what should’ve been an active bar.</description></item><item><title>If There Were No Stars</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/nostars/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/nostars/</guid><description>The phone grew heavy in his hand, threatening to drop from his grip, from the cliff, into that endless expanse below. He couldn’t even see the floor from here; no matter where he looked, it was all the same murky black abyss. At least if he looked up there were stars, dots of light, of something piercing through all of that nothing. Down there… It was just empty.
“Adam?” Adessa’s voice called tentatively from behind him.</description></item><item><title>Mother</title><link>/dennis-site/posts/mother/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/dennis-site/posts/mother/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;In 20 days, my mum dies in an accident on her way home from work. She finishes work at 4 so chances are I&amp;rsquo;ll be in a lecture or doing homework when it happens. My dad would rush home from work when he&amp;rsquo;s called but he works nearly an hour away, by the time he arrives mum might already be dead or at least very close to death. The hospital would do anything they could to help her but eventually she&amp;rsquo;ll succumb to her injuries and my dad will watch her die and he&amp;rsquo;d cry.</description></item></channel></rss>